&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：您好，我们将讨论Web性能。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Hello,
we're gonna talk about web performance.
[咳嗽]第一件事是第一件事。
[COUGH] First thing's first.
我的名字是Steve，我是SendGrid的首席前端工程师。
My name is Steve, and I am a principal
frontend engineer at SendGrid.
我们在SendGrid做了很多事情
We do a bunch of things at SendGrid,
主要业务是每天发送10亿封电子邮件。
the main business is sending
out a billion emails a day.
因此，如果你曾经使用Uber并获得电子邮件收据，我们会将其发送给你。
So if you've ever taken an Uber and gotten
an email receipt, we sent that to you.
或者在eBay上失去了竞标，我们通知了您这一不幸的损失。
Or lost a bid on eBay,
we informed you of that unfortunate loss.
Spotify潘多拉
Spotify, Pandora,
所有这些类型的电子邮件基本上都是通过SendGrid进入您的收件箱。
all of those kind of emails basically go
through SendGrid to get to your inboxes.
简单的思考方式是类似Twillio的东西，但对于电子邮件来说。
Easy way to think about it is
something like Twillio but for email.
我不做这方面的工作，
I don't work on that part,
我在一个富客户端应用程序上工作，用于构建电子邮件。
I work on a rich client side
application for building emails.
这真的很棒，你可以获得在Reaction in中工作的所有优势
Which is really great, you get all the
advantages of getting to work in React in
然后构建应该在Ala2007中呈现的电子邮件。
the modern web and then build emails
that should render in ala 2007.
这很有趣，只是一个有趣的琐事事实是Outlook，你就像，
Which is a lot of fun, just a fun trivia
fact is that Outlook, you're like,
是的，可能使用的是Internet Explorer的渲染引擎。
yeah that probably uses
Internet Explorer's rendering engine.
不，它使用Microsoft Word。
No no, it uses Microsoft Word.
如果你感兴趣的话，我们可以稍后再谈。
So that's something we can talk
about later if you're interested.
但是是的，关于一个大客户的事情，
But yeah, and
the thing about a large client set up,
因为这实际上是我们正在构建的浏览器的桌面应用程序，对吧。
cuz this is effectively a desktop app
that we're building the browser, right.
你会遇到一些有趣的问题。
And you come across some
interesting problems.
几个月前我做了一个关于管理州的研讨会，
I did a workshop a few months
ago on managing state,
您如何管理此应用程序中发生的所有事情？
how do you manage all the things that
are happening in this application?
另一个问题，也是今天的主题，
The other question, and
kind of the theme of today,
就是你如何以一种真正保持表演的方式来做这件事
is how do you do it in a way that
actually stays performant for
用户既使用3，000美元的MacBook，也使用较旧的PC？
users both on a $3,000 MacBook
as well as an older PC?
您如何让它为距离数据中心一步之遥的人工作
How do you have it working for people who
are a stone's throw from the data center
它在芝加哥和世界各地都举办过，对吗？
that it's hosted from in Chicago as
well as across the world, right?
以及应用程序如何保持性能，因为它是活着的
And also how does the application
stay performant as it's alive for
很长一段时间？
a long period of time?
所以我们将查看性能并找出如何
So we're gonna look at performance and
figure out how
我们是否考虑过性能，以及我们将要做出的取舍是什么？
do we think about performance and what are
the trade offs that we are going to make?
有一些完全做这件事和表现将是伟大的，对吧。
There are some totally do this thing and
performance is gonna be great, right.
但很多时候你必须做个交易或者
But a lot of times you have
to make a trade off or
你必须放弃一些东西才能得到一些东西。
you have to give up
something to get something.
根据您正在构建的应用程序类型，
And depending on the kind of
application that you're building,
这些权衡的答案是不同的。
the answer to those
trade offs is different.
所以我们会讨论一下理论，权衡，
So we'll kind of talk a little bit
about the theory, the trade offs,
引擎盖下的东西是如何工作的。
how stuff works under the hood.
因为很多性能建议你只需在互联网上阅读
Because a lot of the performance advise
that you'll just read on the Internet
很可能已经过时了。
could very well be outdated.
如果你只是遵循所有这些事情，只是要求你必须做的事情
And if you just kinda follow all those
things, just mandates that you have to do
在您的应用程序中，很可能他们要么没有帮助，要么
in your application, it's likely
that they're either not helping, or
更糟糕的是，会损害应用程序的性能。
worse, hurting the performance
of your application.